Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society institutional records ARC.288
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 8: Exhibitions and Special Projects, circa 1865-2020
  - Sub-series 8.10: Changing Exhibitions, 1935-2020
    - Landmarks of NY -- [Exhibit Description and Specifications], 2013-2014 (Box 376, Folder 16)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Installation Shots, 2014 (Box 376, Folder 17)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Postcard, 2013-2014 (Box 376, Folder 18)
    - Landmarks of NY -- [Touring Exhibition Agreement], 2013-2014 (Box 376, Folder 19)
    - Documenting Sandy -- Exhibition Planning, 2013 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Documenting Sandy -- Final Images, 2013 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Documenting Sandy -- Submissions, 2013 (Box 377, Folder 3-4)
    - She Said, She Said -- [Budget], 2014 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - She Said, She Said -- [Exhibit Proposal], circa 2014 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - She Said, She Said -- Images, 2014 (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - She Said, She Said -- [Invitations], 2014 (Box 377, Folder 8)
    - She Said, She Said -- [Marketing Proposal], 2014 (Box 377, Folder 9)
    - [Wonder: First Encounters with Green-Wood], 2014 (Box 377, Folder 10)
    - Full Steam Ahead [Ferry Anniversary Exhibit], 2014 (Box 377, Folder 11)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Exhibit Design, 2014 (Box 377, Folder 12)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Images, 2015 (Box 377, Folder 13)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Letter Transcripts, 2015 (Box 377, Folder 14)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Object Research, 2014 (Box 377, Folder 15)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Press Release [draft], 2015 (Box 377, Folder 16)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Public Programs, 2014 (Box 377, Folder 17)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Unused Objects, 2014 (Box 377, Folder 18)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Veteran Outreach, 2014 (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondents -- Visitor Letters, 2015-2016 (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - Jackie Robinson -- Comment Cards, 2017 (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - Jackie Robinson -- [Film Shoot Setup and Schedule], circa 2017 (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Prospect Park -- Visitor Feedback, 2017 (Box 378, Folder 5)
    - The Business of Brooklyn, 2017-2018 (Box 378, Folder 6)
    - Queer Waterfront -- [Budget], 2018-2019 (Box 378, Folder 7)
    - Queer Waterfront -- [Cocktail Party], 2017 (Box 378, Folder 8)
    - Queer Waterfront -- Exhibit Planning, 2015-2016 (Box 378, Folder 9)
    - Queer Waterfront -- Exhibit Script, 2019 (Box 378, Folder 10)
    - Queer Waterfront -- [Exhibition Support Opportunity], 2017 (Box 378, Folder 11)
    - Queer Waterfront -- Object List, 2019 (Box 378, Folder 12)
    - Queer Waterfront -- [Pledges], 2017-2018 (Box 378, Folder 13)
    - Queer Waterfront -- Visitor Feedback, 2019 (Box 378, Folder 14)
    - Builder Levy Exhibit, 2018-2019 (Box 378, Folder 15)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- [Brochure], 2019 (Box 378, Folder 16)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- Listening Parlor at BHS/Arts-focused Exhibition, 2018 September (Box 378, Folder 17)
    - [Muslims in Brooklyn -- Meeting Notes], 2019 (Box 378, Folder 18)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- Postcard, 2019 (Box 378, Folder 19)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- Project Budget, 2017-2019 (Box 378, Folder 20)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- [Project Meeting], 2017 August (Box 378, Folder 21)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- [Project Update], 2017 December (Box 378, Folder 22)
    - Muslims in Brooklyn -- [Schedule], circa 2017 (Box 378, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series 8.11: Unexecuted Exhibitions, 1980-2012
    Materials in this sub-series are arranged chronologically by project. Files for each project are organized alphabetically by folder title.
    Sub-series 8.11: Unexecuted Exhibitions contains correspondence, meeting minutes, object checklists, research files, and other documentation related to proposed exhibitions that were not executed.
    - Performers from Long Island, 1956-1958 (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Manufacturing a Miracle -- Artifact List, 1993 April (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Manufacturing a Miracle -- [Report, Technology for a "Miracle"], 1990 October (Box 379, Folder 3-4)
    - Jazz in Brooklyn, 1992 (Box 379, Folder 5-6)
    - Stonewall History Project, 1992-1994 (Box 379, Folder 7-9)
    - Gay and Lesbian Life in Brooklyn Exhibition Proposal, 1994-1995 (Box 379, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Coney Island Historical Society, 2001 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Grants, 1999-2000 (Box 380, Folder 2-3)
      Contains 1 audio cassette tape.
    - Brooklyn at Play -- [Meeting Notes], 1999-2000 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Object List, 1999 (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Panelist Evaluation Sheets, 2000 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Proposal, 1999 (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn at Play -- Research, 1997-2000 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - John Mackie Falconer Exhibit, circa 2000s (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - Plymouth Exhibit, circa 2000s (Box 380, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Exhibit, 2001-2003 (Box 380, Folder 11)
    - Quirky Objects Exhibit, 2004 (Box 380, Folder 12)
    - Saturday Night Fevers, 2004 (Box 380, Folder 13)
    - 150th Anniversary Exhibit Planning, 2012 (Box 381, Folder 1-2)
    - Post Forward -- Building Tour / History, circa 2012-2013 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - Post Forward -- [Exhibit Script], 2012-2013 (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - Food in Brooklyn [Proposal], 2015 February (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - Behind Closed Doors, 2019 (Box 381, Folder 6)
- Series 9: Oral History, 1987-2019; 2006-2017
  Sub-series 9.1: Administrative Files, 1995-2019, bulk 2006-2015
  Sub-series 9.2: Voices of Brooklyn Oral Histories, 1990-2016, bulk 2006-2008
  Sub-series 9.3: Brooklyn Navy Yard Oral Histories, 2007-2011
  Sub-series 9.4: Brooklyn School of Inquiry, 2006-2016, bulk 2010-2016
  Sub-series 9.5: Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations, 2002-2014, bulk 2011-2014
  Sub-series 9.6: Voices of Crown Heights, 1987-2017, bulk 2015-2017
  Sub-series 9.7: Muslims in Brooklyn, 2017-2019
  The Brooklyn Historical Society began collecting oral histories in 1973 with the Puerto Rican Oral History Project. Following this project, BHS staff collected oral histories on a project basis, primarily for use in exhibitions. In 2006, BHS instituted an Oral History Program with Sady Sullivan as the Director of Oral History (2006-2014). In 2017, BHS launched its oral history portal, which made hundreds of oral history interviews accessible to the public online. Before BHS's merger with the Brooklyn Collection at the Brooklyn Public Library in 2020, the oral history collections included over 1,200 interviews.
  Additional material concerning the Society's oral history work can be found in the following series:
  Series 9: Oral History consists of administrative and project files generated by the oral history program from its inception in 2006 through 2019. It includes policies, procedures, research, correspondence, marketing materials, and project planning documentation related to several extensive oral history projects. The majority of these files were created by Sady Sullivan, Director of Oral History (2006-2014), and Zaheer Ali, Oral Historian (2015-2020).
  - Sub-series 9.1: Administrative Files, 1995-2019; 2006-2015
    Materials in this sub-series are arranged chronologically by year. Files with date ranges are placed according to the latest date found in the file.
    Sub-series 9.1: Administrative Files contains manuals, guidelines, staff training documentation, promotional material, and files pertaining to the planning of various exhibitions, public programs, curricula, and smaller-scale oral history projects. The bulk of these files were created by Sady Sullivan, Director of Oral History (2006-2014), and Zaheer Ali, Oral Historian (2015-2020).
    - Brooklyn Historical Society Oral History Project Excerpts, 1996 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Columbia University Oral History [Curriculum Guide], 2005 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - [Digital Audio Best Practices], 2006 October (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Legacy Oral History Inventory, 2006 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - New York Alumni, 2006 (Box 499, Folder 8)
      Contains signed interview releases for an unidentified oral history project.
      Contains 3 optical discs.
    - Oral History Tape Inventory, 2006 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - Reiff, Henry [Interview Transcript], 2006 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - StoryCorps, 2006 (Box 382, Folder 7)
      Contains 2 DVDs.
    - Grand Scheme, 2006-2007 (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - Randforce Projects, 2006-2007 (Box 382, Folder 9-10)
    - Brooklyn Jazz Project, 2007 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - Sound Directions [Best Practices for Audio Preservation], 2007 (Box 382, Folder 12)
    - Sound Directions [Best Practices for Audio Preservation], 2007 (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Equipment, 2006-2008 (Box 383, Folder 2-4)
    - Interview Guidelines, circa 2006-2008 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - Immigration Week Event Prep, 2007-2008 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - BHS Oral History Curriculum, 2008 (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - Brooklyn Oral History Archive Project [Grant Proposal], 2008 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - [Guide to Collecting Oral Histories], circa 2008 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - Oral History and Performance Conference, 2008 (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - Podcast Manual, 2008 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - School Program, circa 2008 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - Urban Memory Project, 2008 (Box 383, Folder 13)
    - Walking Tour Audio -- Park Slope, 2008 (Box 383, Folder 14)
    - Folk Feet, 2006-2009 (Box 384, Folder 1-2)
      Contains 14 optical discs.
    - [Folk Feet Promotional Material], 2004-2008 (Box 506, Folder 24)
      Removed from Box 384, Folder 1-2: Folk Feet, 2006-2009.
    - Events, 2007-2009 (Box 384, Folder 3)
    - Oral History Inventories, 2007-2009 (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - Oral History Reports, 2007-2009 (Box 384, Folder 5-6)
    - Bed-Stuy Restoration [Interview Questions], 2008-2009 (Box 384, Folder 7)
    - Agreement Form Development, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 8)
    - Digital Storage Projections, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 9)
    - Living and Learning Exhibit, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 10)
    - Narrator Lists, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 11)
    - New Employee Checklist, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 12)
    - OHA Emerging Crises Research Proposal, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 13)
    - [PastPerfect Cataloging Instructions], 2009 (Box 384, Folder 14)
    - Staff Manual, 2009 (Box 384, Folder 15)
    - Starecheski, Amy [Frank Morales Interview], 2009 (Box 384, Folder 16)
    - BHS Articles, 1995, 2010 (Box 384, Folder 17)
    - Hindle, James [Interview], 1998, 2010 (Box 384, Folder 18)
    - BHS Events [Advertisements], 2006, 2008, 2010 (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Puerto Rican Oral History Project, 2008-2010 (Box 385, Folder 2-3)
      Contains 5 DVDs.
    - New Oral History Projects, 2009-2010 (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - Stories of Sports in Brooklyn, 2009-2010 (Box 385, Folder 5)
    - Technology Manuals, 2009-2010 (Box 385, Folder 6-7)
    - Brooklyn Heights Synagogue, 2010 (Box 385, Folder 8)
    - ExLab -- Ebbets Field, 2010 (Box 385, Folder 9)
    - Interviewer Training, 2010 (Box 385, Folder 10)
    - Processing Manual, 2010 (Box 385, Folder 11)
    - Directions for Digitizing Cassettes, circa 2010s (Box 385, Folder 12)
    - [Oral History Association] Classroom Guide, circa 2010s (Box 385, Folder 13)
    - Audio in Finding Aids, 2006, 2011 (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - Oral History Reports, 2008-2011 (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Jewish Historical Initiative [George Harris Interview], 2009-2011 (Box 386, Folder 3-4)
    - Brooklyn Jewish Historical Initiative [Project Planning], 2009-2011 (Box 386, Folder 5)
    - Oral History Strategic Planning, 2009-2011 (Box 386, Folder 6)
    - Walking Tour Audio -- Fort Greene/Clinton Hill, 2009-2011 (Box 386, Folder 7-11)
      Contains 6 optical discs.
    - Board Reports, 2011 (Box 387, Folder 1)
    - Event Releases, 2010-2012 (Box 387, Folder 2)
    - Shirley Chisholm Celebration, 2010-2012 (Box 387, Folder 3)
    - [Shirley Chisholm Celebration brainstorming], circa 2012 (Folder Flat File 3)
    - Oral History Processing Flow, 2011-2012 (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat, 2011-2012 (Box 387, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Civil Rights Oral History Project, 2012 (Box 387, Folder 6)
    - Planning a Listening Party, circa 2012 (Box 387, Folder 7)
    - Prospect Heights, circa 2012 (Box 387, Folder 8)
    - Pro Tools Software, 2006-2013 (Box 387, Folder 9-10)
    - Exhibits with Oral Histories, 2008-2013 (Box 387, Folder 11)
    - 150th Anniversary Program Committee [Meeting Notes], 2013 (Box 387, Folder 12)
    - Microsoft Outlook Manual, 2013 (Box 387, Folder 13)
    - Oral History Quarterly Reports, 2008-2014 (Box 387, Folder 14)
    - BHS Oral History Curriculum, 2014 (Box 387, Folder 15)
    - BLDG92 Oral History Workshop, 2014 June (Box 387, Folder 16)
    - NPS Ellis Island Oral History Proposal, 2014 (Box 387, Folder 17)
    - Oral History Admin Overview, 2014 (Box 387, Folder 18)
    - Public History [Boilerplate Training], 2014 (Box 387, Folder 19)
    - Usage Policy, 2014 (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - Interview Agreement Form, circa 2015 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - [Oral History Association] Annual Meeting, 2015 (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - Sady Sullivan Debrief, 2015 (Box 388, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat, 2015 May (Box 388, Folder 5)
    - Kahn, David [Interview Guide], 2015 (Box 388, Folder 6)
    - Mullin, Susan [Interview Guide], 2015 (Box 388, Folder 7)
    - Kelly, Jessie McClintock [Interview Guide], 2016 (Box 388, Folder 8)
    - Waterfront [Exhibit Planning], 2015-2016 (Box 388, Folder 9)
    - Flatbush + Main Podcast [Flyer], circa 2016 (Box 388, Folder 10)
    - History in Action [Conference Notes], 2016 January (Box 388, Folder 11)
    - Sick [Exhibit Planning], 2016 (Box 388, Folder 12)
    - Oral History Portal Brochure, circa 2017 (Box 388, Folder 13)
    - [Oral History Portal Posters], circa 2017 (Folder Flat File)
    - School Workshop, Intro to Oral History, 2017 (Box 388, Folder 14)
    - Audacity Manual, 2018 (Box 388, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 2018 (Box 388, Folder 16)
    - Narrator Agreement Form, circa 2018 (Box 388, Folder 17)
    - The American Experience, 2013, 2016-2019 (Box 388, Folder 18-22)
      This file contains syllabi, rubrics, and course outlines for a class taught by Zaheer Ali at New York University.
  - Sub-series 9.2: Voices of Brooklyn Oral Histories, 1990-2016, bulk 2006-2008
    The Voices of Brooklyn oral history collection includes interviews collected through several projects undertaken by the Brooklyn Historical Society beginning in 2006. The series started in 2008 as "Brooklyn History Makers" and was renamed in 2016. It features narrators such as civic leaders, artists, community activists, business owners, athletes, veterans, and other Brooklyn residents.
    Voices of Brooklyn oral histories, 2006-2014 (2008.031)
    Sub-series 9.2: Voices of Brooklyn Oral Histories includes interview guides, correspondence, and research materials related to the individuals interviewed for the Voices of Brooklyn oral history series.
    - Bugliarello, George [Research], 1990-2007 (Box 389, Folder 1-2)
    - Gruber, Ruth [Correspondence], 2007 (Box 389, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, Esther Cooper, 2010 (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - Liman, Ellen [Questions], 2007 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - MacCrate, Robert [Research], 2006-2008 (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - Parsons, Richard [Interview Guide], 2008 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - Pearsall, Nancy [Research], 2007 (Box 389, Folder 8)
    - Russell, Carlos [Interview], 2008 (Box 389, Folder 9)
      Contains 2 CDs and 1 DVD.
    - Sahadi, Charlie [Research Notes], 2016 (Box 389, Folder 10)
    - Sobers, Mary DeSaussure [Research], 2005-2009 (Box 389, Folder 11)
    - Tuttle, Faity [Research], 2006 (Box 389, Folder 12)
    - Weston, Randy [Research], 2006 (Box 389, Folder 13)
    - Volkhausen, Grace [Correspondence], 2007 (Box 389, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 9.3: Brooklyn Navy Yard Oral Histories, 2007-2011
    The Brooklyn Navy Yard oral history collection is the result of two collecting projects. The first effort took place from 1986 to 1989. The second effort, spanning from 2006 to 2010, was a partnership between the Brooklyn Historical Society (BHS) and the Brooklyn Navy Yard Development Corporation (BNYDC). This latter project aimed to capture the voices of those who worked at the Navy Yard during World War II and document the evolution of women joining the labor force during the war.
    Brooklyn Navy Yard oral history collection, 1986-1989, 2006-2010 (ARC.003)
    Sub-series 9.3: Brooklyn Navy Yard Oral Histories contains correspondence, interview guides, curricula, and research related to the oral histories conducted by the Brooklyn Navy Yard Development Corporation and the Brooklyn Historical Society from 2006 to 2010.
    - Collection Overview, 2010-2011 (Box 389, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 2009-2011 (Box 389, Folder 16)
    - Curriculum Kit, 2011 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - Digitization, circa 2008-2009 (Box 390, Folder 2)
    - Interview Guides, Checklists, and Correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Interviewee List, 2011 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - Interview Questions, 2007 (Box 390, Folder 5)
    - Joint Interview Agreement Form [Template], circa 2008-2011 (Box 390, Folder 6)
    - Next Imperatives [Interview Guide], circa 2010 (Box 390, Folder 7)
    - Research, 2011 (Box 390, Folder 8)
    - Samples [Excerpts], 2008 (Box 390, Folder 9)
    - WWII Interview Guide, 2010 (Box 390, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series 9.4: Brooklyn School of Inquiry, 2006-2016, bulk 2010-2016
    Materials are restricted until 2125.
    In 2010, the Brooklyn Historical Society partnered with the Brooklyn School of Inquiry (PS/IS 686), a public citywide Gifted and Talented school founded in 2009, to document its growth through oral histories. The resulting collection consists of over 400 interviews with elementary school-age children who attended the school, including annual interviews with the first class as the students progressed through each grade.
    Sub-series 9.4: Brooklyn School of Inquiry includes correspondence, notes, contracts, interview questions, meeting notes, and project planning documentation related to the Brooklyn School of Inquiry oral history project.
    - Interview Kit, 2013-2016 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Media Assets Management Guide, 2015 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - [Project Description], 2010 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - Video Conversion Protocols, 2015 (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - Video Inventory, 2015 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - Year 1, 2009-2010 (Box 391, Folder 6-7)
    - Year 2, 2010-2011 (Box 391, Folder 8-9)
    - Year 3, 2011-2012 (Box 391, Folder 10)
    - Year 4, 2012-2013 (Box 391, Folder 11)
    - Year 5, 2013-2014 (Box 391, Folder 12-13)
    - Year 6, 2014-2015 (Box 391, Folder 14-15)
    - Year 7, 2015-2016 (Box 391, Folder 16)
  - Sub-series 9.5: Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations, 2002-2014, bulk 2011-2014
    Narrator files and releases are restricted until circa 2075, based on the age of the narrator.
    Materials in this sub-series are arranged alphabetically by file title. Releases and narrator files appear at the end.
    Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations (2011-2015) was a multi-year oral history project and public programming series focused on the history and experiences of mixed-heritage individuals and families, cultural hybridity, race, ethnicity, and identity in Brooklyn. Directed by Sady Sullivan, Director of Oral History from 2006 to 2014, the project involved a team of 25 interviewers who conducted over 100 oral history interviews with individuals identifying as mixed heritage. In addition to the interviews, the project produced an interpretive website featuring these oral histories, essays, and educational resources. Funding for Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations was provided by the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), the Institute of Museum and Library Services (IMLS), the New York Council for the Humanities (NYCH), and several other organizations.
    Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations oral history collection, 2011-2014 (2011.019)
    Sub-series 9.5: Crossing Borders, Bridging Generations includes research, promotional materials, financial records, and files related to project planning and website development. It also contains grant documentation for funding received from the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), the Institute of Museum and Library Services (IMLS), and the New York Council for the Humanities (NYCH).
    Additionally, this sub-series consists of narrator files, which include unedited transcripts, checklists, and releases. Narrator files containing unedited interview transcripts and audio recordings are noted at the file level.
    Narrator files and releases were separated. Staff and interviewee tax documentation was destroyed.
    - [90-Day Checklist], 2013 (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - Advisors, 2012 (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Meeting, 2014 June 13 (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - Audio Transcription Center, 2011-2013 (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - August 3, 2011 Meeting (Box 392, Folder 5)
    - BHS Credit Card Receipts, 2013-2014 (Box 392, Folder 6)
    - [BHS Oral History Guidelines and Best Practices], 2011 (Box 392, Folder 7)
    - BK Museum Workshop, 2012 April (Box 392, Folder 8)
    - Blank Release Forms, circa 2011 (Box 392, Folder 9)
    - [Brochures], 2011-2013 (Box 392, Folder 10)
    - [Budget], 2011-2012 (Box 392, Folder 11)
    - [CBBG Wish List], 2011 (Box 392, Folder 12)
    - Consultants, 2013-2014 (Box 392, Folder 13)
    - Critical Mixed Race Studies Conference, 2012 November (Box 392, Folder 14)
    - Curriculum, 2011-2014 (Box 392, Folder 15)
    - Deliverables Workseets, 2012 (Box 392, Folder 16)
    - Essays -- Edits, 2014 May (Box 392, Folder 17)
    - Exhibits, 2012 March (Box 392, Folder 18)
    - Facing Race Conference, 2012 November (Box 392, Folder 19)
    - Glossary of Vocabulary, Tropes, and Landmark Cases, 2013 (Box 392, Folder 20)
    - Historical Context, 2011 (Box 392, Folder 21)
    - IMLS Evaluator Stephanie Downey, 2012 (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - IMLS Grant Finances, 2011-2012 (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - IMLS Proposal, 2010-2012 (Box 393, Folder 3)
    - [IMLS Purchase Orders], 2011-2012 (Box 393, Folder 4-5)
    - IMLS Reporting Schedule, 2011 (Box 393, Folder 6)
    - [In Pursuit of Freedom] NEH Interim Report, 2011 May 2 (Box 393, Folder 7)
    - Income/Expense, 2013-2014 (Box 393, Folder 8)
    - [Interview Descriptions], circa 2014 (Box 393, Folder 9)
    - Interview Team Readings, circa 2011 (Box 393, Folder 10-11)
    - Interviewing Team Bios, 2011 (Box 393, Folder 12)
    - Interviewing Team Survey, 2012 August (Box 393, Folder 13)
    - Listening Log, Walis Johnson, 2013-2014 (Box 393, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Expenses, 2010-2011 (Box 394, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Postcards, 2007-2011 (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - Mixed Families Research, 2010 (Box 394, Folder 3-4)
    - Mixed Heritage Families Planning, 2010-2012 (Box 394, Folder 5)
    - Mixed Heritage Families Programming, 2011 (Box 394, Folder 6)
    - NEH 20th Century Collections [Application], 2011 (Box 394, Folder 7)
    - NEH Advisors, 2010 (Box 394, Folder 8)
    - NEH Implementation, 2011-2012 (Box 395, Folder 1)
    - NEH Implementation: Application/Proposal, 2011 (Box 395, Folder 2)
    - NEH Implementation: Award Letter, 2012 September 4 (Box 395, Folder 3)
    - NEH Implementation: Event Promo, 2012 (Box 395, Folder 4)
    - NEH Implementation: Interview Guide, 2012 (Box 395, Folder 5)
    - NEH Implementation: Interview Team, 2012 (Box 395, Folder 6)
    - [NEH Implementation: Performance Reporting], 2013 (Box 395, Folder 7)
    - NEH Implementation: Promotional Materials, 2012 (Box 395, Folder 8)